fourthhospitality.com 2007-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Fourth Hospitality Software Solutions UK

|  Privacy Policy

This document sets out how we handle your data. You should read it in conjunction with our Terms of Use, of which this Privacy Policy forms part. 

At Fourth Hospitality Ltd ("FH"), we are committed to protecting your privacy. We recognise that your data is of a highly sensitive nature and should be kept confidential at all times. Please read on for more details on our Privacy Policy. This will explain our obligations to you and your obligations to us in relation to security and privacy issues on the Website. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that FH does not own or control, or to people that FH does not employ or manage. However, it does cover our treatment of any personally identifiable information that FH business partners may share with us. 

Acceptance of our Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy explains the data processing practices of FH. Please do read through and understand our Privacy Policy carefully. References to 'you', 'your' and 'yours' are references to (1) the person(s) providing personal information and/or (2) the person(s) whose personal information we hold. References to 'we', 'us' and 'our' are references to FH and Fourth Hospitality Limited. By providing us with personal information, you indicate your agreement, and the agreement of the person whose personal information is being provided, to be bound by our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree our Privacy Policy as set out below, please notify us, do not use our Website and do not provide any personal information to us. 

Collection and Use of your Data 

Data is processed by FH for the purpose of: 

  * Business and Operational use
  * HR
  * Payroll
  * Research, audit and analysis
  * Monitoring and improving the services FH offer
  * Any other matter which is required for the purpose of us providing   
the Services on the terms of our agreement with you

Personal data is also collected and stored for the purpose of managing and calculating your payroll and related tax issues. To calculate payroll we need to gather personal data such as, but not restricted to, name, address, date of birth, National Insurance number, tax code and pay history. This information allows us to manage and calculate the payroll, compile reports and submit in year and end of tax year returns to HM Revenue & Customs when requested. We undertake to design our system in such a way to minimise the use of personal data.   
You acknowledge that FH has the right to scan the user database when required for administrative, advice and invoicing purposes. Disclosure of your Data

We undertake not to sell, trade or rent any personally identifiable information to others. We will send your personally identifiable information to others if: 

  * We need to share your information to provide the service or product you have requested.
  * We need to send the information to others who work on behalf of FH to provide a service or product to you.
  * We find that your actions violate the terms of our Terms of Use or any of our usage guidelines.
  * Our company is subject to a take-over or merger in which case the information will be disclosed to the new owners on the understanding that they will protect the information and only use the information in substantially the same way as previously and will write to you for consent where they intend to use it for any other purpose.
  * We must respond to court orders and any other legitimate request by authorities with which we must comply.
  * The information had been anonymised, pseudomised or otherwise rendered generic.

Reviewing your Data

You can edit your stored data at any time by signing in to the Website and making the necessary changes. You can also request the deletion of your account, as defined in our Terns of Use www.fourthhospitality.com/termsofuse by contacting FH in writing. We undertake to correct, change or delete any inaccurate details upon receiving your reasonable written request to us to do so.   
If information is altered, we undertake to notify the third parties to whom the original information was communicated. We undertake to regularly delete any data that is out of date or no longer required. 

Protecting your Data

We undertake to adopt appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect personal data collected through or stored on our Website. We are fully committed to taking all reasonable steps to protect the security and privacy of any information or data submitted to our Website. We use the latest appropriate Internet security protocol to create a protected connection between you and our servers so that your data can be confidentially sent and retrieved. Once submitted, data is stored on servers and we endeavour to use leading technologies such as, but not limited to, data encryption, firewalls and server authentication, to protect the security of your data. Proper security procedures also provide that we may request proof of identification before we will release any data to you. We undergo periodic reviews of our security policies and procedures to ensure that the FH systems remain realistically secure and protected. Whilst we undertake to maintain the highest possible levels of security practicable to protect data it should be realised that with any data transfer and storage there is always some risk of unauthorised access. FH cannot be held liable for any breach of security. Any information or data submitted to us is done so at your own risk. 

Whilst we have security measures in place to protect your data, it remains your responsibility to keep your user ID and password details secret and to sign off from the Website when you are not using it. 

Use of IP Addresses and Cookies

For security purposes FH automatically records the IP address of your computer each time you visit our Website. 

Cookies are small text files that we can transfer to your computer through your Web browser to enable our systems to 'remember' who you are and to provide personalised features. FH may set and access cookies on your computer. For example, a cookie would be used if you wish your computer to recall your sign in ID each time you visit our Website. You may at any time turn off cookies in your browser. 

Links to third party websites

Our website contains links to other websites. FH is not responsible for the privacy practices, the content or terms of use of these websites. We recommend that you examine the privacy policies and terms of use of these third party websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy

FH reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at anytime without prior notice. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we undertake to post any changes on this page so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Therefore, you should check the Privacy Policy each and every time you access the Website. The Website is owned and operated by Fourth Hospitality Limited a company registered in England and Wales whose registered office is at 1st Floor, Royal Liver Building, Liverpool L3 1PS 

Company Registration No. 3887115   
VAT No. 764526707   
If you have any queries or would like to give us feedback please e-mail us at support@fourthhospitality.com or telephone +44 (0) 8450 556677
